Guide to the Office of the Dean, Washington Square College and Washington Square and University College of Arts and Science 1929-1984 (Bulk 1951-1980) RG.19
New York University Archives
- Series II: Additional Dean's Files, 167548
  - International Student Center, 1968-1975; 168311 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - OE and International Studies, 1969-1976; 168310 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Student Internships, 1976-1981; 168309 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Sample Invitations, 1969-1974; 168308 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Invitations, 1978-1980; 168307 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - WSC Minutes, 1972-1973; 168306 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Italian, 1968-1975; 168305 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Henry James Professorship, 1966-1976; 168304 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Japanese Students, 1967-1974; 168303 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Journalism, 1968; 168302 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Journalism, 1970-1975; 168301 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Journalism Accreditation, 1962-1969; 168300 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Journalism Applications for Graduate Study, 1965-1971; 168299 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - "News Workshop" - Journalism Dept Newspaper, 1967-1971; 168298 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Journalism Fundraising and Gifts, 1970-1973; 168297 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Journalism Proposal for Graduate Course, 1970-1974; 168296 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Junior Science Symposium - U.S. Army Research Office, 1975-1978; 168295 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Misc. "K", 1964-1966; 168294 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Kenan Professorship, 1966-1971; 168293 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Kennedy Foundation, 1964; 168292 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Kerns Colloquium, 1966-1970; 168291 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - The Key Reporter, 1975; 168290 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Martin Luther King Jr., 1968; 168289 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Admissions and Tutoring, 1968-1970; 168288 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Afro-American Student Center, 1968-1971; 168287 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Institute of Afro-American Affairs, 1969-1975; 168286 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Raymond J. Brienza Director of Financial Aid, 1969-1971; 168285 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - MLK Jr. Scholarship Fund, 1968-1971; 168284 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - MLK Jr. Scholarship Program, 1971-1972; 168283 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Klosk, Stanley H Lecturship, 1973; 168282 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Misc. "L", 1962-1963; 226381 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Laboratory Animal Welfare, 1967; 168281 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Laboratory Fees, 1963-1967; 168280 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission, 1974-1976; 168279 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Language Laboratory, 1963-1969; 168278 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Language Placement, 1967; 168277 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Lassen Collection, 1965; 168276 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227098 6
  - School of Law, 1968-1975; 168275 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Legal Counsel - Desai, 1967-1975; 168274 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Legal Counsel, 1975-1979; 168273 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Legislation (Goren), 1972; 168272 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Definition of Liberal Arts, 1971; 168270 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Liberal Studies B.A., 1976-1978; 168269 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Library, 1967-1973; 168268 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Library, 1971-1973; 168267 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Library, 1976-1978; 168266 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Library and City, 1965-1966; 168265 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Library Hours, 1968-1975; 168264 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Bobst Library Privileges Information, 1970-1977; 168263 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Library Programming, 1966-1968; 168262 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Lindback Award, 1966-1968; 168260 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Linguistics, 1968-1975; 168259 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Luncheon, 1968; 168258 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - AB/MBA Program, 1970-1976; 168257 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - NYU in Madrid, 1970; 168256 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs - Jane Maggin, 1971-1981; 168255 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Mathematics, 1967-1975; 168254 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - McKeon, George P., 1967-1969; 168253 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Martin Meisel, 1974-1975; 168252 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Dean Mayerson's Annual Report, 1976; 168251 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Memorial Resolutions, 1968-1973; 168250 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Metropolitan Leadership Program, 1972; 168249 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Metropolitan Studies, 1969-1975; 168248 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Meyer Physics Building, 1971; 168247 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Miller, Saul and Bernard, 1969-1972; 168246 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - WSUC Model Programs - H. Dworkin, Advisement, 1974-1975; 168245 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - James Munn, 1971-1972; 168244 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Music, 1967-1975; 168243 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227099 4
  - Music W/ED, 1971-1972; 168242 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - NSF Survey, 1967-1969; 168241 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - NYU Today, 1973-1977; 168240 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - NSF Proposals Economy and Sociology, 1969-1970; 168239 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - NSF, 1974-1977; 168238 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - New York State Direct Assistance Program, 1969-1974; 168237 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - New York State Education Dept, 1975-1977; 168236 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - New York State Regulations of the Commissioner of Education, 1972-1973; 168235 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - NYU Introduction by Joseph Heller, undated; 168234 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - New York State Visit Re: course practice, 1977; 168233 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Non-Western Studies Project, 1962-1963; 168232 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Norfolk College, 1969; 168231 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Norfolk Evaluation June 19-20, 1965-1969; 168230 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Northeast Conference, 1967-1968; 168229 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Neareastern, 1966-1975; 168228 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Northeast Conference on Higher Education, undated; 168227 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Northeastern Region of Academic Affairs Administrators (ACAFAD), 1974; 168226 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Dean Noss, 1967-1974; 168225 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Nursing Associate Degree, 1963; 168224 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Nursing Baccalaureate Program, 1964-1966; 168223 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Nursing Committee, 1965; 168222 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Nursing Education, 1965-1968; 168221 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Oliva Commission, 1971-1972; 168220 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Oliva Proposals, 1971-1973; 168219 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - O'Mara?, undated; 168218 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Ombudsman, 1969; 168217 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Open Admission, 1969; 168216 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Open Space, 1973-1975; 168215 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Orientation, 1968-1976; 168214 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Michael L. Owen Memorial Prize, 1967-1968; 168213 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Ottendorfer Memorial Fellowship, 1966-1967; 168212 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Overhead Charges, 1968; 168211 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Misc. "P", 1963-1967; 168210 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - PBS for Secondary Schools, 1974-1975; 168209 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04227099 4
  - Parents' Reception, 1967-1973; 168208 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Parsons School, 1963; 168207 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Pass/Fail Option, 1966-1974; 168206 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Peace Corps, 1963-1967; 168205 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Periodical Clippings Re: Universities, 1969-1974; 168204 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Perstare Student Publication, 1973-1974; 168203 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Petitions, 1964-1975; 168202 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Ph.D. Oral Examinations, 1968; 168201 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1968-1977; 168200 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Philosophy, 1968-1975; 168199 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Phonathon, 1972-1973; 168198 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Physics, 1967-1975; 168197 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Politics, 1967-1975; 168196 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Pollock Dinner, 1966; 168195 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Photographic Bureau, 1966-1975; 168194 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Physical Training, 1963-1966; 168193 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Physical Science N1, 1963-1964; 168192 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Placement Careers in Foreign Languages, 1975; 168191 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Plant and Properties, 1963-1974; 168190 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Point Counts - Statistics, 1973-1974; 168189 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Point Count - From Recorder WSUC, 1974-1976; 168188 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Planning Board, 1963-1965; 168187 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227100 0
  - Office for Planning and Development, 1967-1979; 168186 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Director of Planning and Supervising Architect, 1963-1965; 168185 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Portuguese Chair, 1963; 168184 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Posters, 1969-1970; 168183 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Post-Graduate WSC Questionnaire, 1966-1969; 168182 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Pre-Law Program, 1973-1975; 168181 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Pre-Law Society, 1976; 168180 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Pre-Med Program: Statistics, Memos etc., 1974-1975; 168179 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Pre-Medical Scholarships, 1966-1968; 168178 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Pre-Med, Pre-Dent, Pre-Law Scholarships and Awards, 1973; 168177 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Pre-Veterinary Society, 1975; 168176 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - President, 1975-1979; 168175 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - President, 1963-1976; 168174 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Promotion and Tenure Departmental Machinary, 1965-1977; 168173 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Promotional Brochures, 1963-1964; 168172 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Provost, 1966-1967; 168171 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - President's Councils, 1965-1969; 168170 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Presidential Citation, 1963; 168169 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Presidential Convocation, 1968; 168168 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Presidential Reception, 1964-1968; 168167 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Presidential Search Committee, 1975; 168166 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Press Releases, 1975; 168165 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Pre-Teaching Programs, 1963-1965; 168164 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - NYU Programs Abroad, 1969-1976; 168163 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Psychology, 1967-1970; 168162 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Psychology, 1971-1975; 168161 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Publications, 1969-1977; 168160 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Publications Sub-Committee, 1970; 168159 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Publicity, 1972; 168158 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Public Interest Research Group (PIRG), 1973; 168157 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Public Relations, 1964-1975; 168156 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Public Relations Courses, 1966-1969; 168155 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Misc. "Q", 1963-1965; 168154 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Misc. "R", 1964-1974; 168153 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Mabel Rabkin, 1972-1973; 168152 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - AB/DDS Radiation Biology, 1977-1978; 168151 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Race Relations, 1968; 168150 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Rank Order List, 1967; 168149 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Reading Institute, 1964-1965; 168148 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Reading Period, 1967; 168147 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Recommendations/Students, 1973; 168146 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Recommendations/Non-Student, Non-Faculty, 1969; 168145 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Committee on Recommendations to Medical and Dental Schools, 1974-1975; 168144 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Recommedentations to Medical School, 1963-1974; 168143 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Student Records, 1971; 168142 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Recorder, 1968-1976; 168141 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Graduate Count Recorder, 1971-1978; 168140 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Recreational Facilities, 1968; 168139 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Regents College Teaching Fellowships, 1965; 168138 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Regents Graduate Fellowship Programs, 1965; 168137 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Regents Scholarships, 1962-1967; 168136 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Registrar General, 1963-1974; 168135 (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Registrar Enrollment Estimates, 1971-1977; 168134 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Room Assignments, Registration Facilities and Processes, 1968; 168133 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Non-Preregistrants, 1963-1964; 168132 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Pre-Registration, 1963-1964; 168131 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Registration, 1967-1975; 168130 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Registration by Mail, 1964-1967; 168129 (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Interim Reports of Registration, 1968-1975; 168128 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Registration of Undergraduate Programs for Degrees, 1970; 168127 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Registration Procedures, 1974-1975; 168126 (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Registration Statistics (Recorder), 1967-1976; 168125 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227101 8
  - Religion, 1967-1975; 168124 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - The New Republic, 1975; 168123 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Republic Steel (Annual Report), 1974; 168122 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Request by Students to See Records, 1974-1975; 168121 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Requests For, 1966-1970; 168120 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Classified Research, 1966-1967; 168119 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Funds for Research, 1975; 168118 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Sidney Roth Office of Research Services, 1967-1976; 168117 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Estimates of the Projected Sponsored Research and Training Programs, 1971-1972; 168116 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Sponsored Research and Training Programs Manual, 1975-1977; 168115 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Residences, 1963-1976; 168114 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Residence Hall Affairs Enrollment Complaints, etc., 1973-1976; 168113 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Reston Lecture, 1962-1968; 168112 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Chi-Reston Crisis, 1968-1969; 168111 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Resumes, 1975; 168110 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Institute of Retail Management, 1963-1971; 168109 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Retailing Career Day, 1963-1968; 168108 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Dean's Outgoing Interviews - Student Retention, 1977; 168107 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Rhodes Scholarhip, 1963-1973; 168106 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Brooks Roberts, 1965; 168105 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Robinson, Robert, 1965-1968; 168104 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Romance Languages, 1966-1975; 168103 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Rome Summer Session, 1967; 168102 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Delmor Schwarz Reception for Mr. Raphael Rudnick, 1970; 168101 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Air Force ROTC: Metropolitan Area, 1965; 168100 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Misc. "S", 1963-1966; 168099 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - SDS Posters, 1960-1970; 168098 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - S & H Foundation, 1967-1974; 168097 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Safety, 1968-1974; 168096 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Salaries, 1966-1967; 168095 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Sample Letters, 1963-1979; 168094 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Stanely Saplin - Assistant to President, 1969; 168093 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Saturday, 1964; 168092 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Saturday Review, 1960; 168091 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Sawhill Dinner, 1975; 168090 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Schnitzer, Henry R. UC Alumnus, 1973; 168089 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Committee on University Scholars, 1965-1967; 168088 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Scholarships, 1965-1967; 168087 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Committee on Scholarship Awards, 1965-1970; 168086 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Scholarship Funds for Class Entering in Feb. 1975, 1974-1975; 168085 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Committee on Scholarship Standards, 1967-1974; 168084 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Science, Interdiscliplinary, 1972; 168083 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Science Library, 1965; 168082 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Search Committee for New Dean, 1976-1977; 168081 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - FAS Search Committee CVs of Possible Deans, 1977-1978; 168080 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Secretarial Clerical Needs, 1963; 168079 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Mobutu Sese Seko - Distinguished Lecturer Series, 1973-1974; 168078 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Seminar Method, 1963; 168077 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Senate Faculty Council, 1969-1976; 168076 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 1968-1969; 168075 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Senators, 1968-1972; 168074 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - "Senior Drag", 1972-1974; 168073 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Senior Reception, 1968-1974; 168072 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Sentiment, 1968; 168071 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Shakespeare Scholarship Contest, 1963-1966; 168070 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Dean Siegel, 1970-1975; 168069 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Sigma, 1965-1967; 168068 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Singer Company Foundation, 1970; 168067 (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Slavic, 1967-1975; 168066 (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Howard K. Smith Lecture, 1964; 168065 (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - School of Social Work Memorandums - Program Activities, 1975-1978; 168064 (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - Society for the Libraries, 1964-1969; 168063 (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - Sociology, 1967-1975; 168062 (Box 42, Folder 65)
  - Max Solorsy, 1967-1973; 168061 (Box 42, Folder 66)
  - NYU in Spain, 1969-1970; 168060 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227102 6
  - NYU in Spain, 1963-1979; 168059 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - NYU in Spain Contract, 1970-1971; 168058 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Spanish Portuguese, 1970-1976; 168057 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - NYU in Spain, 1963-1979; 168056 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Sponsored Programs, 1975-1978; 168055 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Sponsored Programs, 1978-1980; 168054 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Sponsored Programs Tally Sheets, 1978-1979; 168053 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Student Attrition, 1971; 168052 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Square Journal, 1964-1968; 168051 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - The NYU Staff, 1973-1974; 168050 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - "Staff Newsletter", 1969; 168049 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Staff Relations, 1971-1972; 168048 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Stamm, James R., 1965-1969; 168047 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Standing Committee of the Senate and Senate Rules, 1973-1974; 168046 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Standing Committees, 1968-1974; 168045 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Starr, Wilmarth H., 1963-1969; 168044 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - State Education Dept, 1974-1976; 168043 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - State Education Dept/International Studies, 1969-1970; 168042 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Steering Committee, 1973-1975; 168041 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Sterling Forest, 1963-1965; 168040 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Sterling Forest Music Festival, 1967; 168039 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Strike Correspondence, 1970; 168038 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Strike - Maintence Workers Feb-March 1971, 168037 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Students, 1966-1969; 168036 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Student Activities, 1967-1971; 168035 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Washington Square College Student Council, 1964-1972; 168034 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - WSUC Student Council, 1976-1977; 168033 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Student Directory, 1979; 168032 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Student Faculty Forum, 1970; 168031 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Student Initiated Courses, 1973-1977; 168030 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Job Opportunities for Students, 1976-1977; 168029 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Commission on Student Life, 1969; 168028 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Student Life, 1964-1973; 168027 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227103 4
  - Committee on Student Life, 1965-1976; 168026 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Student Lounge Plans, 1969; 168025 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Student Marketing Plan (Confidential), 1977-1978; 168024 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - WSC Student Partcipation, 1968-1971; 168023 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Student Posters, 1970-1972; 168022 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Students Privacy Rights, 1974-1975; 168021 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Student Projections, 1973-1975; 168020 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - SDS 1960's, 1969; 168019 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Study Group on Advisement and Counseling, 1975; 168018 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Stuyvesant VOICE, 1974-1978; 168017 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Suarez de Puga, 1963-1966; 168016 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Summer Institute, 1968-1974; 168015 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Mailing List for Summer School, 1972-1973; 168014 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Organization of Summer School, 1973; 168013 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Summer Session/ADS, 1973; 168012 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Summer Session, 1974; 168011 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Summer Session, 1975; 168010 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Summer Session, 1976-1978; 168009 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Summer Session 1976 Advertising, 168008 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Summer Session Courses Outline, 1974; 168007 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1972-1975; 168006 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1975-1976; 168005 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1976-1977; 168004 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Sunrise Semester Fanmail, 1969-1971; 168003 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Swimming, 1965-1966; 168002 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Symposium in the Arts and Sciences, 1963-1965; 168001 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - KLM Mrs. Tabor, 1972; 168000 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Take Me Home Rickshaw Poems by Contemporary Poets of Bangladesh, 1974; 167999 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Tamiment Institute Library, 1963-1965; 167998 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Taskforce, 1972-1976; 167997 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Commission on Teacher Education, 1969-1970; 167996 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Commission on Teacher Education, 1964-1972; 167995 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Teachers Ed. CTE Minutes, 1967-1968; 167994 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Teaching Loads, 1963-1968; 167993 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - 1976 TARA Telephone Routes and Codes, 167992 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - David Teitelbaum, 1972-1976; 167991 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Commission to Study Tenure (University of Utah), 1971; 167990 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Tenure, 1960-1979; 167989 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Faculty Tenure, 1971-1972; 167988 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - "La Tertulia Latina", 1970-1971; 167987 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Texas Instruments Foundation Founders Prize, 1974; 167986 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - New York Theological Institute Consortium, 1970-1971; 167985 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - The Third World in Global Context by Prof. Hsiung, 1972-1974; 167984 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227104 2
  - Virgil Thomson Music, 1971-1973; 167983 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - "Ticker", 1969; 167982 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Time Shortened Degree Programs - California State College Questionnaire, 1975; 167981 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Oswald Tippo, 1963; 167980 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Tisch Hall, 1968-1973; 167979 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Tokyo Scholarship, 1963; 167978 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Toven, 1963-1969; 167977 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Town Hall, 1971; 167976 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Transfer Students, 1968-1969; 167975 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer, 1969-1975; 167974 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Trustees, 1968-1977; 167973 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Turkish, 1967-1968; 167972 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Tuition Fees, 1965-1974; 167971 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Tuition Remission, 1964-1970; 167970 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Tutorial Group, 1963-1967; 167969 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Tutoring Program, 1965-1972; 167968 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - High School/College Articulation Program Undergraduate Commission, 1976; 167967 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Committee on Undergraduate Curriculum, 1973-1974; 167966 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate Planning, 1974-1976; 167965 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Planning, 1975-1977; 167964 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Uniform Time Modules Proposal, 1976; 167963 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Union, 1971; 167962 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Union Election May 15, 1970; 167961 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Union Posters, Elections, etc., 1970-1973; 167960 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - United Nations Association of New York, 1975-1976; 167959 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - University, 1963; 167958 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - University College, 1967-1970; 167957 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - University College, 1970-1971; 167956 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - University College, 1971-1972; 167955 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - University College, 1972-1974; 167954 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - The University and the City, 1964-1966; 167953 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on the Use of University Facilities, 1971-1973; 167952 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines, 1970; 167951 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - University of the State of New York, 1966-1975; 167950 (Box 45, Folder 35)